PRIVACY POLICY
==============

Effective Date: 22 August 2019

1. This Privacy Policy explains how we and some of the companies we work with collect, use, share and protect information in relation to our mobile services, web site, and any software provided on or in connection with Selfie2Anime services (collectively, the “Service”), and your choices about the collection and use of your information.
    
2. By using our Service, you understand and agree that we are providing a platform for you to process your content.
    
3. Our Policy applies to all visitors, users, and others who access the Service (“Users”).

INFORMATION WE COLLECT
----------------------

4. We collect the following types of information.
    
5. Information you provide us directly:
    
    1. User Content (e.g., photos and other materials) that you post through the Service. Communications between you and Selfie2Anime. For example, we may send you Service-related emails (e.g., changes/updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices). Note that you may not opt out of Service-related e-mails.
6. Analytics information:
    
    1. We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your device or our Service, including the web pages you visit, add-ons, and other information that assists us in improving the Service. We collect and use this analytics information with analytics information from other Users so that it cannot reasonably be used to identify any individual User.
7. Cookies and similar technologies:
    
    1. When you visit the Service, we may use cookies and similar technologies like pixels, web beacons, and local storage to collect information about how you use Selfie2Anime and provide features to you.
        
    2. We may ask advertisers or other partners to serve ads or services to your devices, which may use cookies or similar technologies placed by us or the third party.
        
8. Log file information:
    
    1. Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you make a request to access (i.e., visit) a web page or app. It can also be provided when the content of the webpage or app is downloaded to your browser or device.
        
    2. When you use our Service, our servers automatically record certain log file information, including your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. We may also collect similar information from emails sent to our Users which then help us track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Service.
        
9. Device identifiers:
    
    1. When you use a mobile device like a tablet or phone to access our Service, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more “device identifiers”. Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device’s operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by Selfie2Anime.
        
    2. A device identifier may deliver information to us or to a third-party partner about how you browse and use the Service and may help us or others provide reports or personalized content and ads. Some features of the Service may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers is impaired or disabled.
        
10. Metadata:
    
    1. Metadata is usually technical data that is associated with User Content. For example, Metadata can describe how, when and by whom a piece of User Content was collected and how that content is formatted.
        
    2. Users can add or may have Metadata added to their User Content including a hashtag (e.g., to mark keywords when you share a photo) or other data.

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
---------------------------

11. In addition to some of the specific uses of information we describe in this Privacy Policy, we may use information that we receive to:
    
    1. provide personalized content and information to you and others, which could include online ads or other forms of marketing
        
    2. provide, improve, test, and monitor the effectiveness of our Service
        
    3. develop and test new products and features
        
    4. monitor metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns
        
    5. diagnose or fix technology problems
        
    6. automatically update the Selfie2Anime application on your device

SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATION
---------------------------

12. We will not rent or sell your information to third parties outside Selfie2Anime (or the group of companies of which Selfie2Anime is a part) without your consent, except as Parties with whom we may share your information in this Policy.
    
13. Parties with whom we may share your information:
    
    1. We may share User Content and your information (including but not limited to, information from cookies, log files, device identifiers, location data, and usage data) with businesses that are legally part of the same group of companies that Selfie2Anime is part of, or that become part of that group (“Affiliates”).
        
    2. Affiliates may use this information to help provide, understand, and improve the Service (including by providing analytics) and Affiliates’ own services (including by providing you with better and more relevant experiences). But these Affiliates will honour the choices you make about who can see your photos.
        
    3. We also may share your information as well as information from tools like cookies, log files, and device identifiers and location data, with third-party organizations that help us provide the Service to you (“Service Providers”).
        
    4. Our Service Providers will be given access to your information as is reasonably necessary to provide the Service under reasonable confidentiality terms.
        
    5. We may also share certain information such as cookie data with third-party advertising partners. This information would allow third-party ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.
        
    6. We may remove parts of data that can identify you and share anonymized data with other parties.
        
    7. We may also combine your information with other information in a way that it is no longer associated with you and share that aggregated information.
        
14. Parties with whom you may choose to share your User Content:  
    i. Any information or content that you voluntarily process with the Service, such as User Content, becomes available to the Selfie2Anime anonymously.
    
15. If we sell or otherwise transfer part or the whole of Selfie2Anime or our assets to another organization (e.g., in the course of a transaction like a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation), your information such as User Content and any other information collected through the Service may be among the items sold or transferred. You will continue to own your User Content. The buyer or transferee will have to honour the commitments we have made in this Privacy Policy.
    
16. We may access, preserve, and share your information in response to a legal request (like a search warrant, court order or subpoena) if we have a good faith belief that the law requires us to do so. This may include responding to legal requests from jurisdictions outside of Australia where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law in that jurisdiction, affects users in that jurisdiction, and is consistent with internationally recognized standards.
    
17. We may also access, preserve, and share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to:
    
    1. detect, prevent, and address fraud and other illegal activity;
        
    2. to protect ourselves, you, and others, including as part of investigations; and
        
    3. to prevent death or imminent bodily harm.
        
    4. Information we receive about you may be accessed, processed, and retained for an extended period when it is the subject of a legal request or obligation, governmental investigation, or investigations concerning possible violations of our terms or policies, or otherwise to prevent harm.

HOW WE STORE YOUR INFORMATION
-----------------------------

18. Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in Australia or any other country in which Selfie2Anime, its Affiliates or Service Providers maintain facilities.
    
19. Selfie2Anime, its Affiliates, or Service Providers may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from Australian law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction.
    
20. By registering for and using the Service you consent to the transfer of information to Australia or to any other country in which Selfie2Anime, its Affiliates or Service Providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.
    
21. We use commercially reasonable safeguards to help keep the information collected through the Service secure. However, Selfie2Anime cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to Selfie2Anime or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
------------------

22. Selfie2Anime does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13. The Service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us.

OTHER WEB SITES AND SERVICES
----------------------------

23. We are not responsible for the practices employed by any websites or services linked to or from our Service, including the information or content contained within them.

HOW TO CONTACT US
-----------------

24. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Service, please contact us through the email [legal@selfie2anime.com](mailto:legal@selfie2anime.com).

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
-----------------------------

25. Selfie2Anime may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it periodically. We may provide you additional forms of notice of modifications or updates as appropriate under the circumstances. Your continued use of Selfie2Anime or the Service after any modification to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such modification.
